boostfin.com 2014-02-09

# BoostFin - Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: 28 th March, 2013**  

### OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. The following policy explains how we deal with the information collected from you, your personal information and options available to you in regard to the policies followed by us. 

### COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION

Any item/paragraph which is not applicable may be deleted   
BoostFin is the sole owner of information collected on this website. We will not share, sell, or trade this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy.   
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of data/information:   
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views; 

(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services ; 

### CONFIDENTIALITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Collection of Information**

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify the client or his company including, but not limited to, User name, telephone number, e-mail address, street address, occupation, and/or industry. 

By giving personal information, the client gives BoostFin consent to collect and use it in accordance with this agreement. 

  * Information Disclosure and Sharing
While, client’s personal information is never shared outside the scope of BoostFin’s business without prior permission, however client’s personal information may be stored and/or processed with supporting companies/services as requested. 
  * Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. However, you are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password. Please do not share your pass word with others. Change your pass word regularly.   
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email. 
  * Your Rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. 
  * Control of Your Password
You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your (ACCOUNT) password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. 
  * Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. The same will be corrected/updated within a reasonable time. 

### RESTRICTED ACTIVITES

Your Information and your activities on the Site shall not: (a) be false, inaccurate or misleading; (b) be fraudulent; (c) infringe any third party's copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights or rights of publicity or privacy; (d) violate any law, statute, ordinance or regulation (including, but not limited to, those governing export control, consumer protection, unfair competition, antidiscrimination or false advertising); (e) be defamatory, trade libelous, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing; (f) be obscene or contain child pornography or, if otherwise adult in nature or harmful to minors, shall be posted only in the Mature Audiences section and shall be distributed only to people legally permitted to receive such content; (g) contain any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs or other computer programming routines that may damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept or expropriate any system, data or personal information. 

### LICENSE

Solely to enable BoostFin to use the information you supply us with, so that we are not violating any rights you might have in that information, you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, sub licensable (through multiple tiers) right to exercise the copyright, publicity, and database rights (but no other rights) you have in Your Information, in any media now known or not currently known, with respect to Your Information. BoostFin will only use Your Information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

### OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use your personal information to facilitate the services you request. We use your personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote safe trading; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our User Agreement; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your personal information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions and for accuracy. 

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site. 

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. 

### COOKIES

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. 

### ADVERTISERS

We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent. 

### LEGAL REQUESTS

BoostFin cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and BoostFin community from bad actors. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, User ID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, address, city, postal code, country, phone number, email, and company name to other participants under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Again, Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

### Notice

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on the Site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. 

### CONTACT

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please contact our support.
